Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI. Irish Memories Radio Program Recordings, 1944-1997; 1.75 Linear Feet; 4.1 Linear Feet in 4 media boxes, 1 record carton, and 1 flat box
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1968-1989
    - Reel 147: Music (Dig. CD 1017, Track 4), undated (Box 87, Reel 147, Box 44, Cd 1017, Track 4)
    - Reel 149: Flag of Sien Fean, Don't Mind If I Do, Men of 20 Say Goodbye, Rattling Bog, undated (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 149)
    - Reel 151: Music (Dig. CD 1019, Tracks 2-11), undated (Box 44, Cd 1019, Track 2-11, Box 87, Reel 151)
    - Reel 153: Chieftains, "Bonapart's Retreat", undated (Box 36, Reel 153, Box 42)
    - Reel 154: "Kilkenny": Theme for Dorothy Hayden Irish Program, undated (Box 44, Box 36, Reel 154)
    - Reel 155: Johnny McEvoy Sends Greetings To Listeners In USA, undated (Box 44, Box 87, Reel 155)
    - Reel 156: Allied Irish Banks Commercials, Mar 1979 (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 156)
    - Reel 157: Irish Tourist Board Commercials, 5 Mar 1976 (Box 87, Reel 157, Box 44)
    - Reel 158: Irish Tourist Board Commercials, Mar 12, 1975 (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 158)
    - Reel 159: Unidentified, Apr 9, 1982 (Box 36, Reel 159, Box 42)
    - Reel 160, undated (Box 42, Box 36)
    - Reel 161: Lord Mayor, Desmond Jennings, undated (Box 36, Reel 161, Box 42)
    - Reel 162: Sean McCarthy, Na Sultoiri, undated (Box 42, Box 87, Reel 162)
    - Reel 163: Unidentified, undated (Box 42, Box 36, Reel 163)
  - Grooved discs, 1937
    - Radio show recordings, 1937-11-13-1953-10-16 (Box 51, Folder 2-8, 25, 28)
- Electronic Records Preservation Masters